good morning and let's look at the top
stocks to watch out for in trade today
starting with Mahindra Mahindra
Financial Services now uh the company
has come out with its Q2 update where
the total dispersements in the month of
sep for in September are at uh 1,900
cross which is up by 23% on a year
on-ear basis with 100% collection
efficiency now overall the Q to
dispersements also are at 6,450 Cross
which is up by 60% so the companies
hopeful for a good Q3 subject to the
Improvement in the auto supply chain is
what they have highlighted surely keep
an eye out on Mahindra and Mahindra
Financial Services on the back of that
update moving on we have Railway wikas
Nigam also which is in Focus after the
company has signed a memorandum of
understanding with Tata steel to
implement the infrastructure projects
either on nomination basis or through a
special purpose vehicle route is what
the company has highlighted so maybe on
the back of this uhou with Tata steel we
could see some movement coming in in the
stock price as well today other than
that sh infra Finance also in
infrastructure Finance also in Focus
after uh RBI um has suspended the board
sh uh Board of sh group companies that
is sh infrastructure Finance sh
equipment Finance owing to the
governance concerns and the uh and the
uh inability to meet their debt
obligations so we could see some impact
coming in on today on sh infrastructure
Finance as well and RBI has said that
they intend to shortly initiate uh
resolution process of the two Shadow
lenders under IBC as well other than
that we do have Hindustan zinc today
which is in Focus as well after the July
to September mind metal production has
risen by around
4% on uh on a your on your basis to
around 248,000 tons from 238,000 tons
previously so mind metal also output has
also risen by 12% sequentially from um
the April to June quarter so surely keep
an eye out on Hindustan sing as well now
we have Vidant also which has come out
with a fure update on production the
production has risen by 21% on a year on
year basis to 5 lak 70,000 tons while
mind Metals output is up by four uh 4%
to 248,000 tons so Q2 overall the
average gross operated oil and gas
production has uh you know is little
changed at
16532 bo uh uh is what the company has
said so surely keep an eye out on that
as well on the back of Q2 update uh jsw
energy also could be in Focus today um
as the company has in in pack with
turbine maker senvion India to buy 59 21
megawatt of onshore wind turbines uh for
the company's renewable energy projects
so surely keeping focus on these stocks
today uh and uh let's keep an eye out on
all these stocks yic bioscience also
could be in Focus uh as The Bard has
approved a proposal for a CeX of around
200 CR for setting up a new
manufacturing plant and unit in indor
madhia Pradesh so all these stocks are
something that you should be keeping on
your radar today at 9:15 a.m.